Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/mohamed-hegazy-134109179 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Next.js Node.js

Express.js

Mohamed Hegazy

Full Stack Developer | MERN Stack

Al Qalyubiyah, Egypt

Summary

As a front-end developer, I have a strong experience with HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, ES6, Bootstrap, React.js, and related libraries such as Axios, Formik, Yup, Material-UI, React Router Dom, and Redux. I have a pleasant experience handling CRUD operations.

Experience

Upwork Frontend Developer April 2023 - Present (10 months)

U Pharma

4 years 2 months

Senior Production Specialist September 2022 - Present (1 year 5 months) 10th of Ramadan, Sharkia, Egypt

Sterile Area Production Specialist December 2019 - November 2022 (3 years) 10th of Ramadan, Sharkia, Egypt

Route

Full-stack Developer December 2022 - October 2023 (11 months)

al rowad pharma QC Specialist November 2019 - December 2019 (2 months) 10th of Ramadan, Sharjah, Egypt

uniswap Production Responsible July 2019 - November 2019 (5 months) al-obour, Egypt

Education

Zagazig University

Bachelor's degree, Chemistry and computer science · (2015 - 2019)